<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-01-30T21:45:11-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">arkmuntasser</title><subtitle>Just a super cool cat doin' some code stuff...</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Punching Nazis is an American Pastime</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/punching-nazi-american-pastime/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Punching Nazis is an American Pastime" /><published>2017-01-23T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-01-23T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/punching-nazi-american-pastime</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/punching-nazi-american-pastime/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/2017-1-23-punching-a-nazi/cap-punching-hitler.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;Captain America punches Hitler, Marvel Comics&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember when Captain America punched Hitler? That was a good time. Fuck Hitler. And fuck Nazis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up there was still a pride in America’s role in WW2. It was the backdrop to a number of movies including Indiana Jones. Hell, there were more consecutive years of games about WW2 than consecutive year in WW2. And in all cases the plot went something like this: Nazis suck balls and America is going to kick some ass. And you know what? We liked it that way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure America had its faults and had screwed up a number thing in the world, but we got one thing totally right. We ended the Nazis. Now, I know I am greatly over-simplifying, but that was the feeling of it. That there was this terrible evil in the world and it was stopped and, though there will always be a new threat, this evil would never return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet here we are. It’s 2017 and Nazis are back. And worse they are home-grown. They don’t even deny being Nazis. Sure they prefer to be called the “Alt-right”, but by there own admission that is purely because “Nazi” doesn’t play well with the youths. Gee, I wonder why that might be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America is not perfect. And it never will be. It’s our duty as citizens to forever strive for a more perfect union. Yes, we are divided now more than ever and it looks like it’s going to be a difficult few years, but there is one thing we simply cannot be divided on: Nazis will not be suffered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Punch a Nazi. They should be afraid and ashamed. We should frighten and shame them back into their hidey-holes. Nazis must never be allowed to make a resurgence. Far too many died for their cause and far too many died to put an end to them. America, do what you do best: kick Nazi ass.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="america" /><category term="punching" /><category term="nazis" /><summary type="html">Indiana Jones killed so many Nazis, like, if it were anyone other than Nazis you would say it bordered on excessive</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/posts/2017-1-23-punching-nazi/cap-punching-hitler.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Nintendo Switch is Beautiful</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/nintendo-switch-beautiful/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Nintendo Switch is Beautiful" /><published>2017-01-14T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-01-14T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/nintendo-switch-beautiful</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/nintendo-switch-beautiful/">&lt;div class=&quot;flex-video&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ao-3D8jmi90&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;sep&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nintendo finally fully reveled their new console, the Nintendo Switch. I have been infatuated with it ever since. I mean, just look at it! That has to be the prettiest looking console every. I thought the Xbox One S was sleek, but this thing is on a whole other level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will admit, I am a sucker for the bright colorful controllers. They really do it for me. There’s a console that is all black and it’ just not as attractive. I can’t wait to pick this up when it drops this March.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s just hope the software is at least half as pretty though I know that’s a lot to ask with Nintendo’s record on UI design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;position:relative;padding-bottom:57%&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://gfycat.com/ifr/FondNegligibleBunny&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; style=&quot;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;sep&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the couple seconds the UI was shown does make me optimistic. Of course this will almost certainly change before release and continue to be even more different post release. Oh well, a girl can dream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;Sources&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;no-bullets&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    The Verge: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theverge.com/2017/1/13/14265722/nintendo-switch-hands-on-photos&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; title=&quot;A closer look at the Nintendo Switch&quot;&gt;A closer look at the Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    Polygon: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.polygon.com/2017/1/13/14261794/nintendo-switch-ui-user-interface&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; title=&quot;Here is exactly 3 seconds of the Nintendo Switch UI&quot;&gt;Here is exactly 3 seconds of the Nintendo Switch UI&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><category term="nintendo" /><category term="switch" /><summary type="html">What are the hex values of that blue and that red?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/posts/2017-1-14-nintendo-switch/bundle_color_tabletop.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Rebuilding My Site</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/rebuilding-my-site/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rebuilding My Site" /><published>2017-01-09T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-01-09T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/rebuilding-my-site</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/rebuilding-my-site/">&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about sex, baby. And by sex, I mean my new website and not sex at all because our personal lives are just that unless the person reading this is, at the time of me writing this, my fiancée then what’s up?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not a designer. Let’s just start there. At one time I wanted to be and even referred to myself as one, but I just am not one. And that ok, because for not being a designer I think I have a pretty good eye for what’s good looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve made and remade my site a number of times over the years and never been happy with the result until now. I finally found the right fonts, colors, and layout that works and helps tell the story of me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think a large part of it was to just embrace the fact that I’m a geek and my site should reflect that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;backend&quot;&gt;Backend&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a static site generated via Jekyll hosted on GitHub pages. I chose Jekyll because it’s simple and I wanted a no-fuss way to get a site and running. I don’t need a whole CMS for my personal site. Aside from the blog, I don’t intend to update very much very often. And where the blog is concerned I would much rather just upload a markdown file and call it a day than mess with some RTE that’s going to riddle my content with BS HTML tags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though this is a static Jekyll site, that doesn’t mean there aren’t cool things going on under the hood. For example, this site has a service worker. Does it need one? No, of course not. I mostly just wanted to learn about service workers and the best way to learn is to do. So, if you’re in Chrome or FF (I think) you should be able to view this offline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a number of improvement I am looking to make to the site going forward. For example, from an accessibility perspective, I am really dropping the ball in many ways. I hope to rectify that in the not too distant future. And I am sure as time goes on I’ll think of a number of bells and whistles to add, but for the launch I really trimmed the site down to the basics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sections&quot;&gt;Sections&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided that there were 4 areas that I wanted to focus on for my site: main banner, projects, blog, and resume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;main-banner&quot;&gt;1. Main Banner&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first major element of the site and I wanted it to be something that would instantly give the visitor a sense of who I was. Rather than have some static image and pithy catchphrase I wanted something that could change and give an insight into my personality. What better than to link it up to my Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technically, it’s not actually connected to my Twitter at all. It’s connected to my Instagram. That’s because it’s easier to grab the url for an image on Instagram than it is on Twitter, but when I post to Instagram those get reposted on Twitter natively anyway. And since I primarily use Twitter, I don’t think it’s unfair to refer to this as my “Twitter” banner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;projects&quot;&gt;2. Projects&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next are my favorite GitHub projects. I am always spinning up repos for new ideas and they are were I do most of my learning. If you wanted to get to know me as a developer, then my work is where you should start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;blog&quot;&gt;3. Blog&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t really blog and never really have. But I’ve always wanted to do. I’ve had various blogs on Tumblr and Blogspot back in the day, but those never really did it for me. I could never get into the community those site were built around. My hope is that by having my blog here with no expectation of a community that I might actually get to using it to actually journal my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure what the balance between personal and professional will be yet, but I’m sure I’ll figure it out as I go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;resume&quot;&gt;4. Resume&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just to provide my bonafides as a developer and show off some of the work I am most proud of having the opportunity to work on and/or lead the development of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;finale&quot;&gt;Finale&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there you have it. A quick break down of my new site. If you have any questions you can tweet at me or email me. Please don’t actually email me because that would be terrible and I’m sure not going to respond to you so just tweet me.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="redesign" /><category term="website" /><summary type="html">A story about a redesign, but also one of self-discovery, but mostly (entirely) the first thing</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Resolutions For 2017</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/resolutions-2017/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Resolutions For 2017" /><published>2017-01-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2017-01-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/resolutions-2017</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/resolutions-2017/">&lt;p&gt;Let’s keep things simple and right to the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deliver more presentations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get in better shape for my wedding (and I guess for the rest of my life too?)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;walk/run more&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;join a gym and make use of it&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get better at a11y&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that’s pretty doable for the year. I’ll check in periodically with updates on how this going and what if any I’ve accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="resolutions" /><category term="2017" /><summary type="html">Personal and professional goals for this coming year</summary></entry></feed>
